Guide to the McKim Mead and White Architectural Records circa 1875-1950 PR 42
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Subseries II.C: 1968 Transfer
    - United States Capitol, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Vanderbilt (Offsite-box II.514)
    - White Church, Hanover, NH (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Williams Pedestal (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Wright, Grosvenor S. (Offsite-box II.514)
      Fund (M16)
    - Anson, Lela Alexander Moore (Offsite-box II.514)
      Ledgerstone (M18)
    - City of Brattleboro, VT (Offsite-box II.514)
      City Hall (M18)
    - Central Park, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.514)
      General (M18)
    - Christ Church, Philadelphia, PA (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Dana, Paul (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Detroit State Bank, Detroit, MI (Offsite-box II.514)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, MA (Offsite-box II.515)
      Bradley Memorial; Expansion Joints; Gates, Classes 1857—1894; Joseph McKean Gates; Yard Gates; Harvard Union; Johnston Gateway; Lowell Bust; Robinson Hall (all M17)
    - Gourlie, John (Offsite-box II.516)
    - Grand Union Hotel (Offsite-box II.516)
    - Hartshorn, S. (Offsite-box II.516)
    - Kane, John Innes (Offsite-box II.516)
    - Neponsit Beach Hospital, Queens, NY (Offsite-box II.516)
    - New York University, Bronx, NY (Offsite-box II.516)
      General; Hall of Fame; Gould Library: Lafayette Bust and Stanford White Doors (all M18)
    - Orange Monument (Offsite-box II.516)
    - Sealy, Galveston, TX (Offsite-box II.516)
    - Thaw, Dr. A. Blair, Sparkill, NY (Offsite-box II.516)
    - Vanderbilt, Frederick W., Hyde Park, NY (Offsite-box II.516)
      Residence (M18)
    - Bowdoin College, ME (Offsite-box II.516)
      Walker Art Gallery (M18)
    - World's Columbian Exposition, Chicago, IL (Offsite-box II.516)
      Agriculture Building (M18)
    - Adams, Edward Dean (Offsite-box II.516)
      Gardener's Cottage; Residence (all M19)
    - Alexander, A.S. (Offsite-box II.516)
      Tombstone (M19)
    - Anacosta Bridge, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.517)
      General (M19)
    - Barclay, Sackett, M., Cazenovia, NY (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Barney, E.J. (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Beebe, J.A. (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Beers, W.H. (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Bennett, James Gordon, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.517)
      New York Herald Building (M19)
    - Bell, Isaac (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Bradford Stables (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Buzzards Bay Bridge, MA (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Christ Methodist Episcopal Church, Pittsburgh, PA (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Farragut Monument, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Goucher College, Baltimore, MD (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Jusserand, Jules Monument (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Kneeland Family, Rutland, VT (Offsite-box II.517)
      Headstones (M19)
    - Miscellaneous (Offsite-box II.517)
      (M19)
    - Rochester American Opera Company (Offsite-box II.517)
    - City of Rochester, NY (Offsite-box II.517)
      City Hall (M19)
    - Thomas Circle Underpass, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.517)
    - World's Fair, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Astor, Vincent, Rhinebeck, NY (Offsite-box II.517)
      General (M20)
    - Blashfield, Edwin H. (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Judson Memorial Church, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Mowbray, H S. (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Madison Square Garden, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.517)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Garden, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box II.518)
    - Bennett, James Gordon, New York. NY (Offsite-box II.518)
      New York Herald Building (M20)
    - Lincoln Memorial, Chicago, IL (Offsite-box II.518)
    - Lincoln Memorial, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.518)
    - Lincoln Statute, London, England (Offsite-box II.518)
    - Oelrichs, Herman, Newport, RI (Offsite-box II.518)
      Residence (M20)
    - United States Military Academy, West Point, NY (Offsite-box II.518)
      Battle Monument (M20)
    - Madison Square Presbyterian Church, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.518)
    - Robb, J. Hampden, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.518)
      Advertising Club of New York (M20)
    - St. Bartholomew's Church (Offsite-box II.518)
      Doors (M20)
    - Phelps Association, New Haven, CT (Offsite-box II.518)
      Wolf's Head Society (M20)
    - Adelphi College, NY (Offsite-box II.519)
      General (675); Dining Hall (669); Nursing School Dormitory (668); N.T. Dormitory (673); Children's Center and Demonstration School (676)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Garden, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box II.519)
      North and South Gates; Washington Avenue (all 45 1/2)
    - Lincoln Alliance Bank (Offsite-box II.519)
      General (M21)
    - Women's National Golf and Tennis Club (Offsite-box II.519)
    - George Washington Hill Pool (Offsite-box II.519)
    - Office Promotion (Offsite-box II.519)
      (M21)
    - Barnard College, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.520)
      General (M22)
    - British Embassy, Washington, DC (Offsite-box II.520)
      Proposed alterations (M22)
    - Chapman Family, Bedford, NY (Offsite-box II.520)
      Headstones (M22)
    - Cutting, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.520)
      Residence alterations (M22)
    - Cutting, Oakdale, NY (Offsite-box II.520)
    - Oelrichs, Herman, Newport, RI (Offsite-box II.520)
      Residence (M22)
    - Benjamin Moore Tablet (Offsite-box II.520)
    - League for Political Education, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.520)
      Town Hall (M22)
    - Watriss, F.N. (Offsite-box II.520)
      Tombstone (M22)
    - Miscellaneous office files (Offsite-box II.520)
      (M22)
    - National City Bank Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box II.521)
    - Registrations, different states (Offsite-box II.522)
      (no #)
    - Architecture Appraisals (Offsite-box II.523)
    - Proposed Work. (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box II.524)
    - Proposed Work. (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box II.525)
      cont'd (no #)
    - 1952 Brochure (Offsite-box II.526)
- Series III: Specifications
  This series includes approximately 63 boxes of specifications, arranged by project. Additional specifications may be found in Series II, Correspondence.
  - Abbey, Thomas (Offsite-box III.1, Folder 1)
  - Adelphi College- administration, recreation, and classroom buildings (Offsite-box III.1, Folder 2)
  - American Military Cemetery, Florence, Italy (Offsite-box III.1, Folder 3)
  - Amherst College (Offsite-box III.1, Folder 4)
  - Amherst College (Offsite-box III.1, Folder 5)
  - Amherst College (Offsite-box III.1, Folder 6)
  - Amherst College (Offsite-box III.2, Folder 1)
  - Amherst College, Chemistry Building (Offsite-box III.2, Folder 2)
  - Amherst College, Dormitories (Offsite-box III.2, Folder 3)
  - Amherst College, Faculty Housing, Merrill Place (Offsite-box III.2, Folder 4)
  - Amherst College, Gymnasium (Offsite-box III.2, Folder 5)
  - Amherst College, Infirmary (Offsite-box III.2, Folder 6)
  - Amherst College, Johnson Chapel (Offsite-box III.2, Folder 7)
  - Amherst College, Library (Offsite-box III.3, Folder 1)
  - Amherst College, Morgan Library (Offsite-box III.3, Folder 2)
  - Amherst College, Pratt Field Gates (Offsite-box III.3, Folder 3)
  - Amherst College, Natatorium (Offsite-box III.3, Folder 4)
  - Amherst College, Power House (Offsite-box III.3, Folder 5)
  - Amherst College, School House (Offsite-box III.3, Folder 6)
  - Amherst College, Service Building (Offsite-box III.3, Folder 7)
  - Amherst College, Squash Courts (Offsite-box III.3, Folder 8)
  - Amherst College, Theatre (Offsite-box III.3, Folder 9)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Offsite-box III.3, Folder 10)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Offsite-box III.3, Folder 11)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Offsite-box III.4, Folder 1)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Offsite-box III.4, Folder 2)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Offsite-box III.4, Folder 3)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Offsite-box III.4, Folder 4)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Offsite-box III.4, Folder 5)
  - Bank of Buffalo (Offsite-box III.5, Folder 1)
  - Bank of Montreal (Offsite-box III.5, Folder 2)
  - Bank of Montreal (Offsite-box III.5, Folder 3)
  - Bank of Montreal (Offsite-box III.5, Folder 4)
  - Bank of Montreal (Offsite-box III.5, Folder 5)
  - Bank of Montreal, NY Branch (Offsite-box III.6, Folder 1)
  - Bank of Montreal, Winnipeg Branch (Offsite-box III.6, Folder 2)
  - Barnard College Dormitories, plumbing and heating (Offsite-box III.6, Folder 3)
  - Barnard College, Greenhouse and Headhouse (Offsite-box III.6, Folder 4)
  - Beard or Lorillard, Tuxedo Park, NY Residence (Offsite-box III.6, Folder 5)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Offsite-box III.7, Folder 1)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Offsite-box III.7, Folder 2)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Offsite-box III.7, Folder 3)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Offsite-box III.7, Folder 4)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Offsite-box III.7, Folder 5)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Offsite-box III.7, Folder 6)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Offsite-box III.7, Folder 7)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Boiler House and Coaling Station (Offsite-box III.8, Folder 1)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Garage (Offsite-box III.8, Folder 2)
  - Bellevue Hospital- hardware schedule, plumbing fixtures, and prints (Offsite-box III.8, Folder 3)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Laundry Building (Offsite-box III.8, Folder 4)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Nurses Training School (Offsite-box III.8, Folder 5)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Outpatient and Female Dormitories (Offsite-box III.8, Folder 6)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Pathological Department (Offsite-box III.9, Folder 1)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Pavilions (Offsite-box III.9, Folder 2)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Pavilions (Offsite-box III.9, Folder 3)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Pavilions (Offsite-box III.10, Folder 1)
  - Blair, E.T., Chicago, ILL (Offsite-box III.10, Folder 2)
  - Blakey Low, Mr. Carroll Residence, New Rochelle, NY (Offsite-box III.10, Folder 3)
  - Bloomingsdale, Lyman G., Mausoleum at Salem Fields Cemetery, NY (Offsite-box III.10, Folder 4)
  - Boston Public Library (Offsite-box III.10, Folder 5)
  - Boston Music Hall (Offsite-box III.10, Folder 6)
  - Bowdoin College, Entrance Gates and Walker Art Gallery, ME (Offsite-box III.10, Folder 7)
  - Bowdoin College, Swimming Pool, Brunswick, ME (Offsite-box III.10, Folder 8)
  - Bowdoin College Union, Brunswick, ME (Offsite-box III.10, Folder 9)
  - Bradford, Lyndsay- stable and cottage (Offsite-box III.11, Folder 1)
  - 60 Broadway (Offsite-box III.11, Folder 2)
  - 38-06 to 38-14 Broadway, Long Island City, NY (building or Wesleyan University, project never built) (Offsite-box III.11, Folder 3)
  - Bronx, Grit Chamber (Offsite-box III.11, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Botanical Gardens (Offsite-box III.11, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Botanical Gardens (Offsite-box III.11, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn Botanical Gardens, Flatbush Avenue Gates (Offsite-box III.11, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn Institute (Offsite-box III.11, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Institute (Offsite-box III.12, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Institute (Offsite-box III.12, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Institute, Duplicates (Offsite-box III.12, Folder 3)
  - Brooks, Phillips- Monument (Offsite-box III.12, Folder 4)
  - Burke Foundations, White Plains, NY (Offsite-box III.13, Folder 1)
  - Burlington City Hall, Burlington, VT (Offsite-box III.13, Folder 2)
  - Butler Art Gallery, Youngstown, Ohio (Offsite-box III.13, Folder 3)
  - Butler Art Gallery, Youngstown, Ohio (Offsite-box III.14, Folder 1)
  - Butler Art Gallery, Youngstown, Ohio (Offsite-box III.14, Folder 2)
  - Century Club (Offsite-box III.14, Folder 3)
  - Church of the Ascension (Offsite-box III.14, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, Avery Building (Offsite-box III.15, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Avery Building (Offsite-box III.15, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, Business Building (Offsite-box III.15, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, Casa Italiana (Offsite-box III.15, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, Chemistry Building (Offsite-box III.15, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, Chemistry Building (Offsite-box III.15, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, Engineering Building (Offsite-box III.16, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Faculty Club, new pent house (Offsite-box III.16, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, Faculty House (Offsite-box III.16, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, Furnald Hall (Offsite-box III.16, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, General (Offsite-box III.16, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, General (Offsite-box III.16, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, Granite step in connection with memorial close, class 1891 (Offsite-box III.17, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Hamilton Hall (Offsite-box III.17, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, Hartley and Livingston Halls (Offsite-box III.17, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, Journalism Building (Offsite-box III.17, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, Kent Hall (Offsite-box III.17, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, Kent Hall (Offsite-box III.17, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, Library (Offsite-box III.17, Folder 7)
  - Columbia University, Library (Offsite-box III.18, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Library (Offsite-box III.18, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, Natural Sciences, Schermerhorn Hall (Offsite-box III.18, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, Natural Sciences, Schermerhorn Hall (Offsite-box III.18, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, Natural Sciences, Schermerhorn Hall (Offsite-box III.18, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, Pharmacy (Offsite-box III.18, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, Philosophy (Offsite-box III.19, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Physics Building (Offsite-box III.19, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, Physics Building (Offsite-box III.19, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, President's House (Offsite-box III.19, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, Students Hall (Offsite-box III.19, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, Students Hall (Offsite-box III.20, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Temporary Laboratory Building (Offsite-box III.20, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, University Hall (Offsite-box III.20, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, University Hall (Offsite-box III.20, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, University Hall (Offsite-box III.20, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, Women's Residence Hall (Offsite-box III.20, Folder 6)
  - Colgate University, Administration Building (Offsite-box III.21, Folder 1)
  - Colgate University, East and West Halls (Offsite-box III.21, Folder 2)
  - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Offsite-box III.21, Folder 3)
  - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Offsite-box III.21, Folder 4)
  - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Offsite-box III.21, Folder 5)
  - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Offsite-box III.21, Folder 6)
  - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Offsite-box III.21, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Medical College (Offsite-box III.22, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Medical College (Offsite-box III.22, Folder 2)
  - Cromwell, Frederic (Offsite-box III.22, Folder 3)
  - Cuban National Hotel, Havana, Cuba (Offsite-box III.22, Folder 4)
  - Cuban National Hotel, Havana, Cuba (Offsite-box III.22, Folder 5)
  - Cuban National Hotel, Havana, Cuba (Offsite-box III.22, Folder 6)
  - Detroit BI-Centennial Memorial, MI (Offsite-box III.23, Folder 1)
  - Downtown Building Company, NY (Offsite-box III.23, Folder 2)
  - Downtown Building Company, NY (Offsite-box III.23, Folder 3)
  - First Presbyterian Church, Chattanooga, TN- wood frames (Offsite-box III.23, Folder 4)
  - Fort Benning Infantry School (Offsite-box III.23, Folder 5)
  - Fort Benning Infantry School (Offsite-box III.23, Folder 6)
  - Fort Greene Park, NY (Offsite-box III.23, Folder 7)
  - Fountain for H.L. Higginson (Offsite-box III.23, Folder 8)
  - Gimbel Building, Subway passage, NY (Offsite-box III.24, Folder 1)
  - Girard Trust Company (Offsite-box III.24, Folder 2)
  - Girard Trust Company (Offsite-box III.24, Folder 3)
  - Girard Trust Company (Offsite-box III.24, Folder 4)
  - Girard Trust Company (Offsite-box III.24, Folder 5)
  - Girard Trust Company (Offsite-box III.24, Folder 6)
  - Girard Trust Company (Offsite-box III.24, Folder 7)
  - Girard Trust Company (Offsite-box III.25, Folder 1)
  - Girard Trust Company (Offsite-box III.25, Folder 2)
  - Girard Trust Company (Offsite-box III.25, Folder 3)
  - Girard Trust Company (Offsite-box III.25, Folder 4)
  - Girard Trust Company, Philadelphia, PA (Offsite-box III.25, Folder 5)
  - Governors Island Hospital, NY (Offsite-box III.25, Folder 6)
  - Governors Island, Hospital, NY (Offsite-box III.26, Folder 1)
  - Governors Island, Infantry Regimental Barracks (Offsite-box III.26, Folder 2)
  - Governors Island, NY Detachment Barracks (Offsite-box III.26, Folder 3)
  - Governors Island, Ventilation Building (Box Flat files, Folder FF91)
  - Hadley Falls Trust Company, Holyokes Mass (Offsite-box III.27, Folder 1)
  - Harlem Valley Hospital (Offsite-box III.27, Folder 2)
  - Harlem Valley Hospital (Offsite-box III.27, Folder 3)
  - Harlem Valley Hospital (Offsite-box III.27, Folder 4)
  - Harlem Valley Hospital (Offsite-box III.27, Folder 5)
  - Harlem Valley Hospital (Offsite-box III.28, Folder 1)
  - Harriman, Ripley. and Company, Air conditioning plant installation (Offsite-box III.28, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Club, Additions and alterations (Offsite-box III.28, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Club, Additions and alterations (Offsite-box III.29, Folder 1)
  - Harvard Club, Additions and alterations (Offsite-box III.29, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Club, Additions and alterations (Offsite-box III.29, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Club, Additions and alterations (Offsite-box III.29, Folder 4)
  - Harvard Club, Ladies Annex- building department papers (Offsite-box III.29, Folder 5)
  - Harvard University, School of Architecture (Offsite-box III.29, Folder 6)
  - Harvard University, School of Business Administration (Offsite-box III.30, Folder 1)
  - Harvard University, School of Business Administration (Offsite-box III.30, Folder 2)
  - Harvard University, School of Business Administration (Offsite-box III.30, Folder 3)
  - Hooker Electrochemical Company, NY Office and Tacoma, Washington (Offsite-box III.30, Folder 4)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Offsite-box III.30, Folder 5)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Offsite-box III.31, Folder 1)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Offsite-box III.31, Folder 2)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Offsite-box III.31, Folder 3)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Offsite-box III.31, Folder 4)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Offsite-box III.31, Folder 5)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Offsite-box III.32, Folder 1)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Offsite-box III.32, Folder 2)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Offsite-box III.32, Folder 3)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Offsite-box III.32, Folder 4)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Offsite-box III.32, Folder 5)
  - Kimball, Mrs. W.W.- monument (Offsite-box III.33, Folder 1)
  - Knickerbocker Trust Company, 34th Street, NY (Offsite-box III.33, Folder 2)
  - Knickerbocker Trust Company, 34th Street, NY (Offsite-box III.33, Folder 3)
  - Library Building, Smithtown, Long Island, NY (Offsite-box III.33, Folder 4)
  - Lincoln Alliance Bank (Offsite-box III.33, Folder 5)
  - Lincoln Monument, Chicago, ILL (Offsite-box III.33, Folder 6)
  - Lincoln Statue, London, England (Offsite-box III.33, Folder 7)
  - Man O' War Statue, Lexington, KY (Offsite-box III.33, Folder 8)
  - McCarren Park Shelter, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box III.33, Folder 9)
  - Metropolitan Club, NY (Offsite-box III.34, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Club, NY (Offsite-box III.34, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Club, NY (Offsite-box III.34, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, NY (Offsite-box III.34, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, NY (Offsite-box III.34, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Addition "E" (Offsite-box III.34, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Addition "G" (Offsite-box III.35, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Addition "H" (Offsite-box III.35, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Addition "J" (Offsite-box III.35, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Addition "K" (Offsite-box III.35, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Carpenter Shop (Offsite-box III.35, Folder 5)
  - Middlebury College, Field House (Offsite-box III.35, Folder 6)
  - Middlesex Hospital, Connecticut (Offsite-box III.35, Folder 7)
  - Middlesex Hospital, Connecticut (Offsite-box III.36, Folder 1)
  - Minneapolis Museum of Fine Arts, Minnesota (Offsite-box III.36, Folder 2)
  - Morgan, J.P. Library, NY (Offsite-box III.36, Folder 3)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Offsite-box III.36, Folder 4)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Offsite-box III.36, Folder 5)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Offsite-box III.36, Folder 6)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Offsite-box III.37, Folder 1)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Offsite-box III.37, Folder 2)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Offsite-box III.37, Folder 3)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Offsite-box III.37, Folder 4)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Offsite-box III.37, Folder 5)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Offsite-box III.37, Folder 6)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Offsite-box III.37, Folder 7)
  - National City Annex, 13 East 42nd Street, NY (Offsite-box III.38, Folder 1)
  - National City Bank, Park Avenue 57th Street, NY (Offsite-box III.38, Folder 2)
  - National City Bank, Fifth Avenue, NY (Offsite-box III.38, Folder 3)
  - National City Bank, 52 Wall Street (Offsite-box III.38, Folder 4)
  - National City Bank, 52 Wall Street (Offsite-box III.38, Folder 5)
  - National City Bank, 52 Wall Street (Offsite-box III.39, Folder 1)
  - National City Bank, 55 Wall Street (Offsite-box III.39, Folder 2)
  - National City Bank (Offsite-box III.39, Folder 3)
  - National City Bank (Offsite-box III.39, Folder 4)
  - National City Bank (Offsite-box III.39, Folder 5)
  - National City Company, 42nd Street and Madison Avenue, NY (Offsite-box III.40, Folder 1)
  - New York Institute for the Blind (Offsite-box III.40, Folder 2)
  - New York Institute for the Blind (Offsite-box III.40, Folder 3)
  - New York Institute for the Blind (Offsite-box III.40, Folder 4)
  - New York Institute for the Blind (Offsite-box III.40, Folder 5)
  - New York Institute for the Blind (Offsite-box III.40, Folder 6)
  - New York Institute for the Blind, Tool/Garden Shed (Offsite-box III.40, Folder 7)
  - New York Institute for the Blind, Pelham Parkway (Offsite-box III.40, Folder 8)
  - New York Institute for the Blind, Lower Level (Offsite-box III.41, Folder 1)
  - New York Post Graduate Hospital (Offsite-box III.41, Folder 2)
  - New York Post Office, Annex (Offsite-box III.42, Folder 1)
  - New York Post Office, Annex (Offsite-box III.42, Folder 2)
  - New York Post Office, Annex (Offsite-box III.42, Folder 3)
  - New York Post Office (Offsite-box III.42, Folder 4)
  - New York Post Office (Offsite-box III.43, Folder 1)
  - New York Post Office (Offsite-box III.43, Folder 2)
  - New York Post Office (Offsite-box III.43, Folder 3)
  - New York Post Office (Offsite-box III.43, Folder 4)
  - New York State Bar Association (Offsite-box III.44, Folder 1)
  - Northwestern Technological Institute, Northwestern University, Evanston, ILL (Offsite-box III.44, Folder 2)
  - Northwestern Technological Institute, Northwestern University, Evanston, ILL (Offsite-box III.44, Folder 3)
  - New York University (Offsite-box III.44, Folder 4)
  - New York University (Offsite-box III.45, Folder 1)
  - New York University (Offsite-box III.45, Folder 2)
  - New York World Fair 1930-1940, Business Code (Offsite-box III.45, Folder 3)
  - Palmer, Mrs. Potter., Mausoleum, Graceland Cemetery, Cook County, ILL (Offsite-box III.46, Folder 1)
  - Payne Whitney Esquire (Offsite-box III.46, Folder 2)
  - Peabody Administration Building, Nashville, TN (Offsite-box III.46, Folder 3)
  - Peabody Fine Art Building, Peabody College, Nashville, TN (Offsite-box III.46, Folder 4)
  - Peabody, George., Demonstration School, Nashville, TN (Offsite-box III.46, Folder 5)
  - Peddie School, Austin Colgate Hall, NJ (Offsite-box III.46, Folder 6)